[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":119763,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":496287,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Do you see how +<sub>6</sub> works? By subtracting 6 every time we get above 5, we ensure t hat when  we combine two numbers using +<sub>6</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 5.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":10029,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":506317,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":39600,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":545918,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":1878,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":547798,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":15665,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":563463,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1018,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":564482,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get y our resu lt.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":15118,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":579601,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":1148,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":580749,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":8190,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":588939,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub>  1 = 2 be cause 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":1018,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":589957,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":4390,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":594348,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":1189,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":595537,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with  the fir st number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":3806,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":599343,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":961,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":600305,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":21762,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":622067,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":1288,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":623355,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":4345,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":627700,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1040,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":628741,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":4702,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":633443,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":3568,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":637011,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger , you su btract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":2835,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":639846,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1022,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":640869,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":30847,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":671717,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the element that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>). Similarly, 3 is its own inverse under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":14120,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":685839,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":4670,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":690509,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":12091,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":702600,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":29021,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":731622,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":17223,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":748846,"internal_chunk_id":"0 -0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":11271,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":760118,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":2734,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":762853,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":7871,"trial_type":"ques tion","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":770724,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1067,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":771793,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":9415,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":781208,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":2123,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":783332,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can simply be performed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":24826,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":808158,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because 1 can make every other element under +<sub>6</sub>, we say that 1 is a  <i>gener ator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br /><br /> However, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":42963,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":851122,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","response_history":["Yes"],"rt":7348,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":858471,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":7973,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":866444,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"Yes","response_history":["Yes"],"rt":1955,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":868399,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":2733,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":871132,"internal_chunk_id":"0- 0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":2959,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":874092,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":1219,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":875312,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":2540,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":877853,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":1139,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":878992,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />Do you see how +<sub>9</sub> works just like +<sub>6</sub>? By subtracting 9 every time we get above 8, we ensure that when we combine two numbers using +<sub>9</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 8.<br /><br />We'll give you one practice question with feedback to make sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to  complete  the remaining questions as accurately as possible.","rt":272837,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":1151830,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":4631,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":1156461,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":1058,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":1157520,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":3812,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":1161332,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9< /sub> 4? ","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":5913,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":1167246,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":3998,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":1171244,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":3472,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":1174716,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":2986,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":1177702,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"5.  I added 4 and 1 and it was smaller than 9 so you keep the lower of the two between 9 and 5.","response_history":["5.  i ADDED","5.  i A","5.  i ","5.  i","5.  I added 4 and 1 and it was smaller than 9 so you keep the lower ot","5.  I added 4 and 1 and it was smaller than 9 so you keep the lower o","5.  I added 4 and 1 and it was smaller than 9 so you keep the lower orf","5.  I added 4 and 1 and it was smaller than 9 so you keep the lower or","5.  I added 4 and 1 and it was smaller than 9 so you keep the lower of the two between 9 and 5."],"rt":35312,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":1213014,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words h ow you g ot your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"3.  I added 8 and 4 then subtracted 9 since the number was higher than 9.  12-9 = 3","response_history":["3.  I added 8 and 5","3.  I added 8 and 4 then subtrat","3.  I added 8 and 4 then subtracted 9 since it was high","3.  I added 8 and 4 then subtracted 9 since it was hig","3.  I added 8 and 4 then subtracted 9 since it was hi","3.  I added 8 and 4 then subtracted 9 since it was h","3.  I added 8 and 4 then subtracted 9 since it was ","3.  I added 8 and 4 then subtracted 9 since it was","3.  I added 8 and 4 then subtracted 9 since it wa","3.  I added 8 and 4 then subtracted 9 since it w","3.  I added 8 and 4 then subtracted 9 since it ","3.  I added 8 and 4 then subtracted 9 since it","3.  I added 8 and 4 then subtracted 9 since i","3.  I added 8 and 4 then subtracted 9 since the number was n","3.  I added 8 and 4 then subtracted 9 since the number was higher than 9.  ","3.  I  added 8  and 4 then subtracted 9 since the number was higher than 9. ","3.  I added 8 and 4 then subtracted 9 since the number was higher than 9.","3.  I added 8 and 4 then subtracted 9 since the number was higher than 9.  12-9 = 3"],"rt":36875,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":1249890,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0.  This one is hard, i had a hard time understanding the identity without the explanation in front o f me. sorry","response_history":["0.  This one hi","0.  This one h","0.  This one is hav","0.  This one is hard, i har","0.  This one is hard, i had a hard time s","0.  This one is hard, i had a hard time understanding the identy","0.  This one is hard, i had a hard time understanding the identify ","0.  This one is hard, i had a hard time under standing  the identify","0.  This one is hard, i had a hard time understanding the identif","0.  This one is hard, i had a hard time understanding the identiti","0.  This one is hard, i had a hard time understanding the identity without the explanation in front o f me. sorry"],"rt":53304,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":1303194,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"14.  14 - 9 is 5 from the inverse would have to be 14 in order to get the 5.","response_history":["14.  14- 8 -","14.  14- 8 ","14.  14- 8","14.  14- ","14.  14-","14.  14 - 9 que","14.  14 - 9 qu","14.  14 - 9 q","14.  14 - 9 is 5 from the inverse would have to be 14 in order to get the 1","14.  14 - 9 is 5 from the inverse would have to be 14 in order to get the 5."],"rt":58393,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":1361587,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"11.  11 - 9 equals 2 so it has to be 11 in order to end up with 2","response_history":["11.  11 - 9 qe","11.  11 - 9 q","11.  11 - 9 equals 2.","11.  11 - 9 equals 2 so it has to be 11 in order to end up with 2"],"rt":46158,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":1407745,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"9.  9-9 = 0","response_history":["9.  9-9 = 0"],"rt":12304,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":1420050,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"12.  I added 3 and 12 to get what i would have to subtract 9 from in order to end up with 3. ","response_history":["12.  I added 3 and 12 to get what i would have to subtract ","12.  I added 3 and 12 to get what i would have to subtract 98 ","12.  I added 3 and 12 to get what i would have to subtract 98","12.  I added 3 and 12 to get what i would have to subtract 9 from in order to end up with 3. "],"rt":36954,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":1457004,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"yes.  because i am able to get 4 with two","response_history":["yes.  because i wa","yes.  because i w","yes.  because i am able to get 4 our ","yes.  because i am able to get 4 our","yes.  because i am able to get 4 ou","yes.  because i am  able to  get 4 o w","yes.  because i am able to get 4 o ","yes.  because i am able to get 4 o","yes.  because i am able to get 4 with two"],"rt":63407,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":1520411,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no, i cannot make 1, 2 3 4 or 5 with it.","response_history":["no, i ac","no, i a","no, i cannot make 1, 2, ","no, i cannot make 1, 2,","no, i cannot make 1, 2 3, ","no, i cannot make 1, 2 3,","no, i cannot make 1, 2 3 4 or 5 with it."],"rt":13443,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":1533855,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":" no, i ca nnot make anything else with it.","response_history":["no, i cannot make anything else with it."],"rt":10332,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":1544187,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"yes.  i can get to 2 with it","response_history":["yes.  i h","yes.  i can get to 2 with it"],"rt":10182,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":1554369,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use +_n, and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":29921,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":1584291,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"1 + 6 7.  6 would be N ","response_history":["1 + 6 5.  6 would be ","1 + 6 .  6 would be ","1 + 6 7.  6 would be  ","1 + 6 7.  6 would be N "],"rt":78641,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":1662933,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"Im not sure how to do this one.","response_history":["Im not sure how do ","Im not sure how do","Im not sure how d","Im not sure how to do this one."],"rt":30611,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":1693545,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"its 1, 2, 3, 4, 5","response_history":["its 1, 2, 3, 4, 5"],"rt":22864,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":1716409,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":8799,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":1725209,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":4426,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":1729636,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a divisor of n, that is, x must divide n evenly, with no remainder.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","response_history":["True"],"rt":7102,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":1736740,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words why your answer is correct.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"True","response":"I would think true, but im not entirely sure. ","response_history":["I would think true, but i m not ex ","I would think true, but im not enti","I would think true, but im not entri","I would think true, but im not entr","I would think true, but im not entirely sure. "],"rt":63941,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":1800681,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Sometimes","response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":14683,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":1815365,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words why your answer is correct.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"somet imes","response":"sometimes.  i would think it could be sometimes but not always.","response_history":["sometimes.  ii would","sometimes.  ii woul","sometimes.  ii wou","sometimes.  ii wo","sometimes.  ii w","sometimes.  ii ","sometimes.  ii","sometimes.  i would think it could be sometimes.","sometimes.  i would think it could be sometimes= ","sometimes.  i would think it could be sometimes=","sometimes.  i would think it could be sometimes but not always."],"rt":93454,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":1908819,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Sometimes","response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":31606,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":1940425,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press Continue to continue.","rt":6096,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":1946521,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"33","response_history":["33"],"rt":2063,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":1948584,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"High school diploma","response_history":["High school diploma"],"rt":10277,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":1958863,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"High School Algebra","response_history":["High SChool","High SChoo","High SCho","High SCh","High SC","High S","High c","High School Alger","High School Algegra","High School Algegr","High School Algeg","High School Alge","High School Alg","High School Algebra"],"rt":49240,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":2008104,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, reme mber and  understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","response_history":["2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","1 - never heard of it"],"rt":6367,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":2014471,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","response_history":["2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was"],"rt":4789,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":2019262,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 -  not at a ll","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"3 - definitely","response_history":["3 - definitely"],"rt":2986,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":2022248,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":2154,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":2024402,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"3 - definitely","response_history":["3 - definitely"],"rt":1931,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":2026333,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What  is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Male","response_history":["Male"],"rt":1903,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":2028237,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"English","response_history":["English"],"rt":3276,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":2031514,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No pen or paper, that would probably be why I did so poorly on some of it....","response_history":["BN","B","No pen or paper, that would probably be why i did","No pen or paper, that would probably  be why  i di","No pen or paper, that would probably be why i d","No pen or paper, that would probably be why i ","No pen or paper, that would probably be why i","No pen or paper, that would probably be why I did so poorly on the ","No pen or paper, that would probably be why I did so poorly on the","No pen or paper, that would probably be why I did so poorly on th","No pen or paper, that would probably be why I did so poorly on t","No pen or paper, that would probably be why I did so poorly on some of it...."],"rt":16185,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":86,"time_elapsed":2047699,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I enjoyed it and thought I had more of it understood until the instructions were taken away and then not so much.  Thank you!","response_history":["I enjoyed it. ","Thank you/!","Thank you/","Thank you!. ","Thank you!.","Thank y ou!  IO e","Thank you!  IO ","Thank you!  IO","Thank you!  I enkjpo","Thank you!  I enkjp","Thank you!  I enkj","Thank you!  I enk","Thank you!  I enjoyed it and thought i had ","Thank you!  I enjoyed it and thought i had","Thank you!  I enjoyed it and thought i ha","Thank you!  I enjoyed it and thought i h","Thank you!  I enjoyed it and thought i ","Thank you!  I enjoyed it and thought i","Thank you!  I enjoyed it and thought I had more of it une","Thank you!  I enjoyed it and thought I had more of it understood until the instrcut","Thank you!  I enjoyed it and thought I had more of it understood until the instrcu","Thank you!  I enjoyed it and thought I had more of it understood until the instrc","Thank you!  I enjoyed it and thought I had more of it understood until the instructions were talk","Thank you!  I enjoyed it and thought I had more of it understood until the instructions were tal","Thank you!  I enjoyed it and thought I had more of it understood until the instru ctions w ere taiken","Thank you!  I enjoyed it and thought I had more of it understood until the instructions were taike","Thank you!  I enjoyed it and thought I had more of it understood until the instructions were taik","Thank you!  I enjoyed it and thought I had more of it understood until the instructions were tai","Thank you!  I enjoyed it and thought I had more of it understood until the instructions were taken away and then not so much.","I enjoyed it and thought I had more of it understood until the instructions were taken away and then not so much.  Thank you!"],"rt":36769,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":87,"time_elapsed":2084469,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"}]